<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TEI xml:space="preserve" xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" 
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" 
xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0 https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kermitt2/grobid/master/grobid-home/schemas/xsd/Grobid.xsd"
 xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink">
	<teiHeader xml:lang="en">
		<fileDesc>
			<titleStmt>
				<title level="a" type="main">BEYOND AGILE: CONTINUOUS DELIVERY MODELS FOR ENTERPRISE SALESFORCE IMPLEMENTATION</title>
			</titleStmt>
			<publicationStmt>
				<publisher/>
				<availability status="unknown"><licence/></availability>
			</publicationStmt>
			<sourceDesc>
				<biblStruct>
					<analytic>
						<author>
							<persName><forename type="first">Bhavana</forename><surname>Kandukuri</surname></persName>
							<affiliation key="aff0">
								<orgName type="institution">State University of New York</orgName>
								<address>
									<settlement>Binghamton</settlement>
									<country key="US">USA</country>
								</address>
							</affiliation>
						</author>
						<title level="a" type="main">BEYOND AGILE: CONTINUOUS DELIVERY MODELS FOR ENTERPRISE SALESFORCE IMPLEMENTATION</title>
					</analytic>
					<monogr>
						<idno type="ISSN">3050-8797</idno>
					</monogr>
					<idno type="MD5">9B3E99B592471396C84D0522C7B09244</idno>
					<idno type="DOI">10.5281/zenodo.18850690</idno>
				</biblStruct>
			</sourceDesc>
		</fileDesc>
		<encodingDesc>
			<appInfo>
				<application version="0.7.2" ident="GROBID" when="2026-03-11T21:05+0000">
					<desc>GROBID - A machine learning software for extracting information from scholarly documents</desc>
					<ref target="https://github.com/kermitt2/grobid"/>
				</application>
			</appInfo>
		</encodingDesc>
		<profileDesc>
			<textClass>
				<keywords>
					<term>Continuous Delivery</term>
					<term>Enterprise Salesforce Implementation</term>
					<term>DevOps Automation</term>
					<term>Platform Engineering</term>
					<term>Pipeline Orchestration</term>
				</keywords>
			</textClass>
			<abstract>
				<p>The shift towards Continuous Delivery patterns from conventional Agile methods is a paradigmatic shift in enterprise Salesforce implementation strategies. This article investigates how CD patterns solve the exponential complexity problems of large-scale Salesforce implementations by leveraging architectural ingenuity, automated tooling systems, and organizational change. The combination of platform engineering concepts and DevOps techniques produces an environment where development teams attain unprecedented deployment speed while upholding strict quality metrics. By virtue of source-controlled development, automated testware frameworks, and advanced pipeline orchestration, organizations transcend the inherent constraints of sprint-based Agile methods that are handicapped by metadata dependencies, regulatory compliance mandates, and multi-environment designs. Implementing dedicated Salesforce DevOps platforms, with Git-based version control systems and continuous integration servers, creates end-to-end automation strategies that have a profound impact in minimizing manual intervention and speeding up feedback loops. Aside from technical deployment, CD drives radical organizational changes in terms of culture, eliminating silos and enabling cross-functional communication through collective ownership of deployment results. With this change, businesses can respond to the forces in the market and regulation and satisfy the needs of the consumers in a timely fashion, and importantly, decrease the risk of failure due to their test automation and gradual deployment. The strategic value is achieved in terms of increased responsiveness of the organizations, employee satisfaction, and sustainable competitive advantage in unstable markets.</p>
			</abstract>
		</profileDesc>
	</teiHeader>
	<text xml:lang="en">
	</text>
</TEI>
